there is an opportunity for you to move to log Zembroke free of charge without spending any money.
So if you're interested in moving to log Zembroke or you know anyone who is interested in moving to
log Zembroke please watch this video till the end and share this video to them. Don't be selfish
because this is a very very lucrative opportunity a very wonderful opportunity that nobody needs to
miss. So this opportunity requires you to do what have a minimum of three years post secondary school
qualification. So you must have done a post maybe a diploma or BSC that's after your secondary school.
You must be above 18 years before you can be eligible for this program. This program is called
training chip and there are currently about four of them currently on. See them being displayed on
the screen and they cover those in the inter IT law, banking and finance. If you are interested
gather your documents and use the link I will leave in the comment section. Pay attention to
this part I want to talk now. Use the link I will leave in the comment section. This link will enable
you to apply for all but please you are not allowed to apply for the four. You can only apply for the
three. The best suits your needs or meets your qualification. If you apply for four of them
at once you will be what you will be disqualified. If you apply for four you will be disqualified so
do not apply for four. And you need a Europe pass CV before you can apply for this because log Zembroke
is located in Europe. So you need a Europe pass CV. That's the CV that is recommended for this
particular application. If you don't know how to get your Europe pass CV drop it in the comment
section that you need help for your Europe pass CV and I will connect you to who can help you with
your Europe pass CV. And the number of requirements you need is your police character certificate.
If you don't know how to get your police character certificate please drop it in the comment section
and I will link you off to someone that will help you get your police character certificate
within 48 hours, within 48 hours. So please share this video. Don't be selfish and use the link
out in the comment section for this application. Do your due diligence and reach true. Write your
motivational statement. That is your statement of intent or statement of purpose or motivational
letter whichever one you want to call it. Write it, object your CV. Make sure you have not walked
you have not benefited from this program before and make sure you have not walked with any European
company before applying for this. So this is very suitable to those that are still in Nigeria or
in Africa or wherever you're watching me from and you've not had anything to do with any European
company previously. Okay. All right. Thank you very much and see you in my next one.